Hello um
YouTube friends, Facebook
uh friends. Good evening. Good evening.
Um I am just uh jumping on to take
another few minutes like I did a couple
of uh days ago, actually last week to um
let you know
about the revelation in seven days
course that is coming up. Um, it was
going to be starting this Sunday, but uh
because of some uh travel issues, I
wasn't able to start the Daniel in seven
days until Monday. That is seven days.
So, that's going to go through until
Sunday. Meaning
that instead of Revelation in seven days
starting on Sunday evening, this coming
Sunday, it will be starting on Monday
evening. However,
if you have not signed up yet, I want to
encourage you to do so. Um we are on
night number three of our Daniel in
seven days study. And uh I tell you
these classes um
they are really
really powerful.
Um tonight
tonight I'm going to be sharing
something with my Daniel in seven days
class that I have not shared before ever
anywhere. and um they are they will be
hearing it for the first time and uh
they're excited. Uh so when I say these
classes are going really well
um I strongly encourage you uh if you
want more than a surface understanding
of the book of uh Daniel or revelation.
Uh the Daniel class has already started.
So this go around it it is I would say
it's too late. You could still join
but um I would say wait until the next
Daniel class. But the Revelation one has
not started yet. That starts this coming
Monday.
And I would strongly encourage you if
you want to get a deeper understanding
of the book of Revelation, like I shared
in my previous uh previous live that one
of the key things for me in studying
prophecy when I came into this church
was not just understanding the what, but
understanding the why. And I'll tell you
guys, it's a beautiful thing to see
people in this class who say, "Hey, I've
never really been able to grasp the book
of Daniel." um after two hours of
teaching say things like I have never
heard Daniel like this before. Um I
understand it at a depth just from one
class. I understand it um from a depth
that I have not understood it from
before.
And uh we have seven nights of this. So
to hear people responding like that
after night one um is is a tremendous
blessing. So,
how do you sign up for the class? Um,
I'm going to put the link in the
description after this video is
uploaded, but I'll say it here as well.
The link is my photoology.com.
my photoology.com.
Uh, if you go to that site, you will see
the Daniel class, you will see the
revelation class, and you will see the
date for that class. It is uh two hours
of teaching every night.
So, seven nights, two hours of teaching,
live teaching, interactive teaching. For
those of you that sign up for the class,
you will have access to all the
recordings. Um, you will have access to
the PDFs. Um,
but most of all, you will have access to
a deeper understanding of this book. So,
listen you guys, I'm teaching Daniel and
Revelation all the time, right? Um you
can go to my YouTube page and find
information there. But what I'm doing
with this class
um I'm doing in a very concentrated
way in which I can't really do um in
another setting. This is live. It is
interactive question and answers. Uh so
it's just a different setting alto
together than what I typ typically put
out there. But having said that even if
you watch put out there, I promise you,
your understanding of Daniel and
Revelation is going to get better.
However,
if you want to really go beyond the
surface, I'm again going to encourage
you to join this class. Um,
and I will leave it there. So, I got to
actually get ready for tonight's class.
And tonight's class, you guys, again,
um, you know, we try not to make these
classes too big so that we can I can
interact with each student. Um,
so that's why I'm doing multiple
classes, right? Same classes over and
over. So, if you miss this one, you can
get the ne you can get into the next
setting, the next class, which will
probably be in January. Um, but
tonight's class I am super excited about
because uh it's on Daniel 7. And you
would think, well, we know what we need
to know about Daniel 7, but I promise
you,
yeah, tonight is going to be different.
and you will eventually hear it because
I I will def I will eventually share
this um
with the public, but they get to be uh
they get to be the first hearers of this
very powerful study tonight on Daniel 7.
So, uh with that said, guys, peace. I'm
gonna again put the link to the um to
the uh study um or to the class, I'm
sorry, uh in the comments or under the
description of the YouTube video in the
comments on Facebook. So, if you want to
join uh Revelation in seven days, you
can feel free to do so. If you still
want to join the Daniel class, we are
only on night
tonight is going to be night three. And
I would say
we got an hour and 20 minutes before
that class starts. Sign up if you want
to, but if you miss tonight, I would
definitely say wait until the second
wait until the next class around um
where I'll do Daniel in seven days again
um and sign up for the whole thing. All
right, so with that said, guys, I will
um say have a good evening and uh be
blessed. Hope to see you in class